We now return to
The Adventures of Aquaman.
- Yeah?
- Hey, can you grab me another beer?
Yeah. Anything else?
Maybe, you know, TV Guide,
you know, another pillow for your feet
or something?
No. Actually, you know what?
Get me, like, a Dewar's and soda, and,
you know, try to keep the saltwater
out of it, if you could.
- Try to keep the saltwater...
- Yeah.
We're surrounded by saltwater, you know.
It's kind of difficult.
I know. I'm just saying,
I'm just saying, try.
Yeah, okay, I'll try.
- You want me to wipe your ass, too?
- Oh, that's a helpful tone.
I'm just saying, you're kind of abusing
your powers a little bit, don't you think?
Actually, this is all time that
could be spent getting me my beverage.
Hey, what are you guys doing?
We got to get ready for your grandpa's
80th birthday dinner.
- Peter, calm down. He's just your father.
- Yeah, but I love him.
His folksy racism,
his I-don't-care-where-I-am flatulence.
And the way it always seems like
he's chewing,
even when there's no food in there.
- Hiya, Dad.
- Francis, it's so good to see you.
Lois, you haven't changed a bit,
you lying bitch.
Francis, why don't you come
into the dining room, huh?
The table's all set for your birthday dinner.
Lois, actually, Dad said
he would prefer it if you did not join us,
you know, you being a Protestant and all.
He said it's okay if you sit
at the kid's table.
Peter, I cooked the damn dinner.
You know, I knew you were going to
react like this, and that's why
I brought Bill Lumbergh
to explain it to you.
Yeah, I'm going to need you to go ahead
and not complain about this.
Oh, and if you could go ahead
and sit at the kids' table,
that'd be great.
I'm just saying, '70s boobs were different.
I don't know.
You know, it wouldn't kill you
to contribute to the conversation.
Dad, tell us about World War I and how
America defeated Kaiser Permanente.
Lois, when are you going to
get that baby baptized?
Oh, God, not this again.
Francis, why the hell is this always
an issue with you?
Because I love this family and
I don't want my grandson to burn in hell.
I love you, Grandpa. Your toenails
are the same color as my school bus.
You really think that
splashing magic water on Stewie
will keep him out of hell?
Watch that kind of talk
or you'll get your heathen head smacked.
Oh, that's very Christian.
- "Believe what I say or I'll hurt you. "
- Now you're getting it.
Peter, we have a problem.
Hey, hang on, Lois. I'm watching a movie.
And now back to Jaws V,
Fire Island.
- You think we should be this far out?
- Stop worrying, Mark. We'll be fine.
Hey, I'm gonna eat you all.
I'm gonna eat that hairy leg.
I'm gonna eat that one, too.
Oh, I can see right up them shorts.
I got a whole bunch of rows of teeth
to chew you with.
Oh, now wait a minute. I did have
a chubby kid on a raft earlier today.
It's okay, though.
I've been swimming a lot lately.
Yummy.
Peter, your father won't let up
about Stewie getting baptized.
I am sick of him always trying to force
his religious views on us.
All right, I'll talk to him, Lois,
but, you know,
when my father wants something,
it's like sex with Kobe Bryant.
You can kick and scream all you want,
but it's gonna happen.
- Dad, what are you doing?
- There's no cross in here.
Every kitchen needs a crucifix.
Oh, yes. Nothing says, "Eat up,"
like a bleeding, half-naked Jew
nailed to a piece of wood.
Listen, Dad, I gotta talk to you.
Lois was wondering if maybe you could,
I don't know, ease up on the whole,
you know, Jesus-ay Christ-ay,
if you catch my drift.
You're a lapsed Catholic, Peter.
Your wife's a Protestant whore
and your baby isn't even baptized.
All right, look, Dad,
I don't want you to hate me, all right?
So I'll make a deal with you.
If we get Stewie baptized, you and
all other old people have to acknowledge
and be aware that there's crap
in the corners of your mouth.
I'll think about it. Now let's go.
Old people are gross, no matter how cute
they try to make them look
on Desperate Housewives. Go ahead.
Switch over to ABC for five seconds.
I'll wait. I'll wait five seconds.
Oh, my God, did you see?
Did you see how old and ugly they are?
Oh, my God, that redhead looks like
somebody pulled Silly Putty
over their knee.
I'm sorry, Mr. Griffin,
but I can't baptize little Stewie today.
It turns out our last shipment
of holy water is tainted.
Tainted? Holy water?
How did that happen?
We'll call you
when we get a new shipment in.
There's no such thing
as tainted holy water.
Come on. We'll do it ourselves.
Stewie Griffin, I baptize you in the name
of the Father, the Son and the Holy Ghost.
- And Space Ghost.
- What are you doing?
Oh, my God! This is almost as bad as
my bath with Kathy Bates.
Yeah, I think I'm going to get out.
Stewie, you don't look so good.
Oh, baby, you're burning up! Oh, my God!
Stewie, Stewie, speak to me!
Don't... Don't take me to a black doctor.
Mr. And Mrs. Griffin,
I've examined your son
and he is suffering from
a temporary toxic anemia
which has substantially weakened
his immune system.
Is he gonna die?
No, but he's highly vulnerable to infection
and must be quarantined
in a germ-free plastic environment.
My God, you mean like John Travolta
in that movie?
Oh, no, you're gonna take his face off,
like in Face/Off?
Well, it looks like the operation
was a success.
Do you know what the best part of this is?
Try licking yourself.
You bastard!
Peter, he meant
The Boy in the Plastic Bubble.
How could this have happened?
It's obvious to me that Stewie's
been exposed to tainted holy water.
Peter, you had Stewie baptized
behind my back?
Come on, honey.
This is no worse than
when I rented out your uterus
to those inner city immigrants.
Peter, you're a complete slave
to your father's religion.
What about your religious beliefs, huh?
You have a choice, you know.
- I do?
- Of course. You're a grown man.
- You can pick any religion you want.
- Really?
You know, Lois, maybe you're right.
Maybe I should pick my own religion.
The question is, which one?
I'll tell you what you can pick.
A tune out on that piano.
Oh, now how the whiz-bang
does the rest of it go?
Quick! Make something up!
Peter, what are all these women
doing in our living room?
Lois, I took your advice
and picked a new religion.
- I'm gonna be a Mormon.
- A Mormon? Are you sure?
Come on. Nailing a different wife
every night? That's a no-brainer.
Oh, Lois, this is Kimmy,
the checkout girl from the Korean market.
Nancy, our postal carrier.
And you know Tiffany,
the filthy woman who stands downtown
and screams at traffic.
I ate a tube of Crest for dinner!
Isn't she funny? She's definitely
the Kramer of my Mormon wives.
- Nancy, get me a beer.
- Mormons aren't allowed to drink alcohol.
Peter, did you just
throw those women away?
No. Maybe.
Also in the news,
some trouble at St. Phillips Church.
That's right, Diane.
A shipment of tainted holy water
could put some local babies in jeopardy.
Sounds dangerous, Tom.
Be careful next time you're at confession
telling the priest
about cheating on your wife
with that Filipino drag queen.
Well, at least you're in no danger, Diane,
since you only visit church
to leave your self-delivered, unwashed,
half-dead newborns on the back step.
Coming up, how to turn
your unwanted change into folding money.
You know, it's kind of sad seeing Stewie
in that plastic bubble.
- I think he looks like a bunny.
- Oh, that's it, Chris, keep laughing.
When I get out of here,
you're going to get it.
I'll lull you into a false sense of security
like those network television announcers.
Tonight
on an all-new Mama's Family,
Mama's got more than she can handle
with the in-laws in town.
A deadly fire
could spell death for a honeymoon couple
on an all-new Hotel.
Tonight on Newhart,
the stockings are stuffed with comedy
when Bob has to play Santa Claus.
Then, a sniper's bullet
threatens a partnership
on an all-new Cagney and Lacey.
Tonight on a laugh-out-loud Night Court,
love is in the air when Judge Harry's
old high-school flame comes to town.
Then, a child's death could mean
the case of Arnie Becker's life
on an all-new L.A. Law.
That's Night Court at 8:00.
L.A. Law at 9:00.
Now remember, kids, don't touch Stewie.
He's not allowed to have
any human contact.
Hey, finish the job, idiot!
For God's sakes, there's no ventilation!
It smells like Brian Dennehy in here!
I see London, I see France,
I see Stewie's unsightly chapped ass.
Hey, gay-bo, I'm up here. Up here.
Hi, my name's Peter.
I'm a Jehovah's Witness,
here to spread the good news
of the story of Jesus Christ.
- Okay, go ahead.
- Really?
Wow.
Boy, you're the first person
who didn't slam the door on me.
Okay, well,
Jesus was a miracle worker, of sorts.
He would travel from place to place,
putting things right that once went wrong
and hoping each time that his next leap
would be the leap home.
What do you think you're doing
with my wife?
Oh, boy.
The pathway to enlightenment
starts with an unfettered, focused mind.
- Look out!
- What are you doing?
Oh? I thought that dot on your head
was from a sniper rifle.
Peter, this spot is a sacred adornment.
It's a portal, an opening through which
all light, goodness, rejuvenation,
joy and ecstasy
may enter the human form.
- A vagina?
- Get out.
Hey, Stewie, 3:00. Time for The View.
No! No, no! Not again!
Let me out of here!
I can't watch another second!
Relax, Stewie. The doctor gave me this
so you can get some exercise.
Boy, Stewie's more wound up than
Dad was that time he took steroids.
Peter, could you please pass the potatoes?
Damn it, Meg!
Now, back to Happy Days.
- Ah, that Fonzie is magic.
I love the way he hits the jukebox
to make it work.
What is it, Mr. C?
Fonz, I wanted to pleasure Marion
for our anniversary, but, as you know,
I have erectile dysfunction.
- Oh, there we go.
- Thank you, Arthur.
Eh.
Brian, will you carry me upstairs?
I want to look at my toys.
- No. I'm watching television.
- Come on, I'm sick.
All right. Come here.
Oh, Todd, I feel like we'll never have
a baby of our own!
We will, Kelly.
You just have to visualize it.
Come on, close your eyes.
Picture a happy, healthy baby boy at play.
Now put him in a magic bubble
and release him to the universe.
Honey, now I want you to visualize
Lindsay Lohan,
only, naked
and doing a backwards crab-walk.
- What?
- Just do this for me!
Ah, Peter! Where have you been, lad?
Well, Dad, I was trying to find
my own religion, but it didn't work out.
I haven't been this disappointed
since I lost my virginity.
Uh-oh.
You want to get some breakfast
or something?
You want to find religion,
all you got to do is look in your heart.
Who's always been there for you,
offering wisdom and truth?
You've known him all along, Son.
Now worship him!
Oh, my God! Dad's right!
There is only one person and it's time
for him to be properly worshipped.
I, Peter Griffin, hereby establish
the First United Church of the Fonz.
Fonzie, if this be your will, give me a sign.
Hi, I'm Lindsay Lohan.
This is how a crab walks.
It sure is! Fonzie be praised!
All right, Dad.
Two days ago, this was an old barn.
And now, thanks to you,
it's an old barn with a sign on it.
All things are possible through
the Lord God, Arthur Fonzarelli, Son.
- So, you're really going through with this?
- Absolutely.
You know this place only cost me $100?
That's a better deal than that
Aaron Neville megaphone I bought.
Okay, I wanna thank you guys for
making me Activity Director for the day.
Okay, first of all, can...
What the hell?
What the hell's wrong with this thing?
Okay, we're about to start the...
Peter, it's not a good idea
to be putting these flyers all over town.
People are gonna think you're crazy.
Hey, how'd you like to lose
a bunch of teeth?
I'm sorry, Lois, that was way more than
what was called for,
but that's what happens
when you challenge someone's faith.
Oh, Peter, I know this is important to you,
but I don't wanna see you humiliated.
I don't think anyone's gonna
wanna worship the Fonz.
- Is this the Church of the Fonz?
- Yes, it is.
I read your flyer.
Finally, a religion that makes sense to me.
Hey, everyone. I found him. Over here.
Oh, there you are. You would not believe
the morning I've had.
What in blazes is this?
I thought you said
we were going to church.
This is church, Francis, a new church,
created by a man who was brave enough
to follow his own vision.
Please rise.
Now sit on it.
The Fonz be with you.
And also with you.
- Let us "Eh. "
- "Eh. "
Wow, I can't believe
people are actually buying this.
Hey, Fonzie's cool, Brian.
You see, deep down, I think we all
secretly yearn to be Italian and stupid.
A reading from the letters
of Potsie to the Tuscaderos.
Yea, and did Fonzie downstairs cometh
from his apartment above the garage.
And sayeth he, " Reassembleth will I
the pieces of my motorcycle,
"though I suffereth
from temporary blindness.
"And yea, for I am holy,
befriendeth I will Sticks Downey,
"the only negro in the state of Wisconsin. "
Amen.
- Brian, what's that smell?
- Black spray paint.
- What were you painting?
Oh, you think you're so funny.
Well, as soon as I figure out where I am,
you're dead, Brian!
Damn it, I haven't been this dizzy
since I did those helium whippets
at that birthday party.
Okay, okay, ready? Here goes.
I'm a female. I have a high voice.
I have reproductive organs inside of me.
And I buy groceries.
Peter, your religion is an abomination.
I never thought you could ever
embarrass me more in a church
than you did
at your cousin Mary's wedding.
And if anyone knows of any reason
why these two should not be married,
let him speak now.
Really?
Nobody's gonna speak up.
I'm the one who's gonna have to say it.
All right.
Genital warts.
But, Dad, you're the one who said
I should look into my heart
- to find my religion.
- Yes. Real religion.
What I saw today wasn't religion.
It was just a bunch of sheep, singing songs
and listening to ridiculous tall tales.
- Actually, that is religion.
- Shut your trap, Brian.
Hah! You tell him.
- Why? I agree with you.
All Peter's done is found another way
to exploit people's ignorance,
and that's just wrong.
You think I'm...
See, Brian,
that's a word the Fonz can't say,
because all is right
when you welcome Fonzie into your life.
Fonzie be with you.
I ought to take off my belt
and slap the crap out of him.
Look, Francis.
I don't like you and you don't like me.
But I suggest we set aside our differences
and work together.
I have an idea
of how to snap Peter out of this.
Work together? You and me?
Sure, sometimes opposites
work well together.
In fact, Peter taught me that.
Reverend Peter, I gotta talk to you.
Last night I had sex with a teenage blonde
and her mother.
Well, that's quite a story, Quagmire,
but my church doesn't have confession.
So there's really no reason
for you to tell me.
Are you kidding? I'm telling everybody.
Giggity Goo Ga!
Let us pause to reflect
on the sacred mystery
of Richie's elder brother, Chuck,
who ascended the stairs
with his basketball in Season One
and never came down again.
There's just one problem, Peter.
When a religion gets too powerful,
it's bound to have imitators.
What are you talking about?
Hi. I'm Sherman Hemsley
and I've just established
the Church of George Jefferson.
Who wants to move on up?
Hi, I'm Gavin MacLeod
and I've just established
the Church of Captain Stubing.
Who wants to come onboard?
Hi, I'm Kirk Cameron.
Oh, great. You here to convert people
to the Church of Mike Seaver?
No, I'm here to convert people
to Christianity.
Okay.
Well, he was on Growing Pains.
I can't believe it. Everybody's gone.
Well, people like that
are always looking for the next voice
to tell them what to do.
And here I was,
thinking I was making a difference.
I thought I was actually connecting
with people.
Could there be anyone stupider than me?
- Madonna?
- Oh, yeah. She's pretty stupid.
That's something we can all agree on,
right?
- Absolutely, yeah. Francis?
- Oh, major idiot. Major idiot.
Yeah, yeah. Well, gosh!
I guess we do have some common ground
here after all, huh?
Yeah. And La Isla Bonita, not a real place.
I looked it up. Couldn't find it.
- Bought a globe. Couldn't find it.
- Oh, yeah? That makes her a liar, too.
- She's awful.
- Awful, awful woman.
- I agree, yeah.
- And she's a whore.
- Oh yeah, big time.
- Oh, everybody. Canseco?
- Dennis Rodman.
- Dennis Rodman, right. Right, yeah.
Rodman? My God!
I think he lost all his money, didn't he?
Rodman lost? You sure
you're not thinking of MC Hammer?
No, no, I think... Well, him, too.
I read somewhere, I think it was in like,
like Stuff, or is it...
No, no, no. You know what,
it was on Real Sports with Bryant Gumbel.
And they said that
he's in the poorhouse now, yeah.
You think she'd do him now?
What, would Madonna do Rodman now?
Oh, yeah, no,
'cause it's not about the money.
It's about pissing off Daddy.
That's right. She's got a lot of problems.
- Lot of problems.
- Yeah, we are smarter.
- We are smarter than Madonna.
- Oh, no question.
Well, I should probably get out
of these robes.
- Oh, look at you. You're all better.
- That's right, Brian. And you are toast.
I'm gonna get in the gym, get my lats back
and then me and my friends from
Cobra Kai are gonna take you down, man.
Listen, sorry I had to rain on your parade,
Peter.
It's all right, Brian.
I guess the Church of the Fonz
was just a bad idea.
Not really, Peter. You were preaching
honesty, friendship, courage.
And if you manage to inspire
even one person to embrace those values
then you are a success.
Thanks, Lois.
But I doubt there's any chance of that.
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru